guitartutee.com 2013-04-15

# Privacy Policy Chords Tabs Lyrics | GuitarTutee | Guitar Tutorial Videos, Chords, Tabs, Lyrics. Sing With Us.

_information_  
GuitarTutee is continuously committed to protecting the privacy of it’s visitors. We do not sell, distribute or give out any of our visitors information. The following discloses how information is collected and used on and throughout our web site. Aside from the case where you explicitly give permission to provide your contact information to a third party, any personal information you provide on this site will only be known to yourself and GuitarTutee. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

_personal information and demographics_  
GuitarTutee does not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address, unless you actively provide this by filling out registration forms. 

However, GuitarTutee does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as your IP address, your browser type and operating system, and the address of the web site that referred you to GuitarTutee. This information is collected as a whole for a broad range of general statistical uses; for providing potential advertisers with audience statistics, for administrating the web site, providing more-focused in-demand content, and to track abusive users. 

_registration/contributions_  
A user or visitor that submits content to GuitarTutee must first be a registered member and hence provide their name and a working e-mail address, along with account information and optional personal details. All information provided, except passwords, may be listed on the web site and should be considered public. 

_polls and voting_  
None of these features require you to provide any personal information, however GuitarTutee stores your IP address along with your answer or vote. This is solely to avoid multiple votes from the same person, and GuitarTutee will never disclose your IP address to anybody else. 

_disclaimer_  
This site contains links to other sites and GuitarTutee can not be held responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. 

_further information_  
If you have additional questions regarding your privacy on GuitarTutee, feel free to contact us by going to the Contact Page.
